(Sheldon:)Scrimmage.
(Sheldon:)The line of scrimmage
is the imaginary transverse line...
...separating the offense
from the defense.
(Leonard:)Oh.
(Howard:)Sheldon knows football?
(Leonard:)-Apparently.
-I mean, Quidditch, sure. But football?
(Leonard:)-Sheldon, how do you know this stuff?
-I grew up in Texas.
(Sheldon:)Football is ubiquitous in Texas.
There's pro football, college football,
high school football, peewee football....
(Sheldon:)In fact, every form of football
except the original, European football.
(Sheldon:)Which most Texans believe
to be a commie plot.
(Leonard:)-Unbelievable.
-If interested...
(Sheldon:)...I also know all about frying meat
that isn't chicken as if it were chicken.
(Leonard:)So you could teach me?
(Sheldon:)Football or chicken-fried meats?
(Leonard:)Football. I'm going to Penny's
to watch a game with her friends.